Guide to the Lincoln Steffens Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III. Letters of Lincoln Steffens
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Ella Winter, 1922 June 17, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 June 17, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 June 29, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 July 6, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1922 July 10, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 July 10, (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 July 21, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 August, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 August 25, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1922 August 30, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1922 September 7, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 September 9, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1922 September 10, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1922 September 14, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 September 23, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1922 September 7, (t.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1922 September 27, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 October 12, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1922 October 17, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1922 October 23, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1922 November 7, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1922 November 19, (t.l.s.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1922 November 25, (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1922 November 30, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 December 12, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1922 December 17, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 December 19, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 January 13, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 January 17, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 January 23, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1923 January 28, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 February 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 February 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 February 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1923 February 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 February 16, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 February 18, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 February 23, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 February 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1923 March 3, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 March 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 March 12, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1923 March 13, (a.l.s., 1p., with envelope) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1923 April 19, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 April 23?, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 May 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 May 10, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 May 12, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 May 14, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 May 15, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 May 25, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1923 June [7], (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 June 20, (a.l.s., 2p., with a note in the hand of Etta "Gussie" Nobbes) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1923 June 21, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 July 5, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1923 July 15, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 July 27, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 August 9, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 August 21, (t.l.s.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1923 August 28, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 August 30, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 October 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 October 4, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1923 October 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 October 29, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1923 November 1, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 November 16, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 November 29, (a.l.s.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1923 December, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1923 December 6, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1923 December 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 December 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1923 December 28, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 January 9, (a.l.s., 5p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 January 19, (a.l.s.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, circa 1924 January 21, (a.l.s., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 January 23, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 January 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 February 26, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 March 12, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 March 20, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1924 April 3, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 April 6, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 April 16, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 April 17, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 April 19, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 May 2, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 May 6, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1924 May 16, (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 May 23, (a.l.s., 5p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 May 29, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 June 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 June 13, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 June 21, (a.l.s., 6p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 June 25, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1924 June 29, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1924 July, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 July 9, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1924 July 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 July 22, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 July 28, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1924 August 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1924 August 4, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 August 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 August 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 August 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1924 August 7, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 August 7, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1924 August 8, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1924 August 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1924 August 12, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1924 August 15, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1924 August 17, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 August 23, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1924 August 24, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 August 31, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1924 September 4, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 September 10, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 September 13, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 October 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1924 October 7, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 October 12, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 October 18, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1924 October 19, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1924 October 22, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 November 8, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1924 November 21, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Rosa [Winter?], 1924 November 24, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 November 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 November 29, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Rosa Winter, 1924 December 8, (a.l., 1p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 December 14, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1924 December 19, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1924 December 19, (t.l.s.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1924 December 20, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1924 December 20, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 January 1, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 January 5, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 January 9, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 January 25, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 January 26, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 February 2, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 February 6, (t.l.s., 4p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 February 9, (t.l.s., 2p., with related item) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 February 11, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 February 15, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 February 17, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 March 3, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 March 11, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 March 21, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 March 22, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope and related item) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 April 2, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 April 5, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 April 6, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 April 12, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 April 12, (t.l.s., 3p., signed "Peter Stanley") (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 April 17, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 May 1, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 May 5, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 May 11, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 May 11, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 May 17, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 May 18, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 May 26, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 June 1, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 May 18, (t.l.s., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 June 10, (t.l.s.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 June 10, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 June 21, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 June 27, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1925 June 28, (t.l.s.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 June 21, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 July 5, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1925 July 22, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 July 23, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 August 7, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 August 19, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 August 19, (t.l.s., 3p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 September 8, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 71)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1925 September 13, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 September 17, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 September 24, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1925 September 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1925 September 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1925 September 26, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1925 September 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Ella Winter, 1925 September 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Pete Stanley Steffens and Ella Winter, 1925 September 29, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 October 8, (a.l.s.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 October 9, (t.l.s., 4p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 October 13, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 October [19], (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), circa 1925 October 19, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 October [26], (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 November 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1925 November 17, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 November 18, (t.l.s., 3p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 November 21, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), circa 1925 November 25, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1925 November 29, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 December 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1925 December 8, (t.l.s., 4p., with note in the hand of Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James)) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 December 17, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1925 December 24, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 71)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 January 12, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1926 January 12, (t.l.s., 3p., signed "Pete") (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 January 27, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 January 31, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 February 2, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 February 3, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
  - Winter, Ella-- To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 February 3, (t.l.s., 1p., on bottom of above letter) (Box 72)
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 February 20, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 February 20, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 February 25, (t.l.s., 6p.) (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 March 7, (t.l.s., 6p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 March 10, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 March 17, (t.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 March 31, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1926 April 3, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 April 4, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 April 6, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 April 12, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1926 April 18, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 April 25, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 May 4, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 May 9, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 May 13, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 May 16, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 May 19, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 May 30, (a.l.s., 8p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 June, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1926 June 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 June 13, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 June 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Pete Stanley Steffens, 1926 June [14], (t.l., 2p., with typed signature) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 June 15, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 June 15, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 June 16, (t.l., with typed signature) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 June 17-18, (a.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 June 18, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 June 19, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 June 20, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 June 21, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 June 21, (a.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 June 24, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 June 24, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 June 25, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 July 2, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 July 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 July 2, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 July 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 August 4, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 August 4, (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 August 18, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 August 18, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 August 26, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 August 27, (t.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 August 28, (t.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 August 28, (a.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1926 August 28, (a.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 August 31, (t.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 September 7, (a.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 October [3], (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 October 5, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 October 7, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 October 12, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1926 October 15, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 October 22, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 October 29, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 November 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 November 15, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 November 25, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 November 28, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 November 28, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 December 4, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1926 December 6, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1926 December 10, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 December 12, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1926 December 12, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1926 December 14, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1926 December 24, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1927 January 2, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)